

BRENT VANWILDEMEERSCH JAVASCRIPT ENGINEER

DETAILS

Brussels, Belgium

vanwildemeersch.bre nt@gmail.com

vanwildemeersch.bre nt.github.io

LANGUAGES

Dutch NATIVE French **PROFICIENT FLUENT** English

SKILLS

JS/TS (Vue.js, Angular, React, ReactNative, ES6 Redux, Vuex, Styled Components, Storybook)

HTML5, CSS, LESS/SASS

Cypress, Jest

Git, CI/CD, DevOps basics Linux and Windows

CERTIFICATIONS

Professional Scrum Master (PSM1)

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

PROFILE

Javascript software engineer with 5 years of experience. A dedicated problem solver and expert skills in Javascript and supporting languages/libraries and frameworks that solve real world problems through code. Eager to learn and always open to explore new things

Flexible person who can adapt quickly to changing circumstances

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Problem solver and strong communicator. Eager to prove my value and talent. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through challenging projects. I enjoy working collaboratively, but can run projects independently. Focused on developing scalable and well-documented software solutions

EDUCATION

2013 - 2017 Bachelor of New Media and Communication Technologies

Hogeschool West-Vlaanderen - Kortrijk, Belgium

Industrial Sciences 2007 - 2013

Vrij Technisch Instituut- Poperinge, Belgium

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (FOR POSITIVE THINKING COMPANY)

November 2020 - Current | Easyfairs

Brussels, Belgium

- Development and maintenance of inhouse products used by clients and by staff
- · Working with product owners to re-architect and rebuild an VueJS app to
- Development and architecture of prototypes for new features and future projects
- · Working with team members to improve development and documentation of
- Writing automated tests to improve reliability and customer satisfaction
- Collaborating with backend, devops and security team to improve workflows and security

JAVASCRIPT SOFTWARE CONSULTANT

September 2020 - Current | Positive Thinking Company

Brussels, Belgium

- Guidance of junior Javascript developers in their growth path
- Part of the internal Javascript community
- Sharing knowledge during KSS (Knowledge Sharing Sessions) about software development, architecture to other consultants, Business Managers, ...

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

July 2017 - August 2020 | Ocular

Zwevezele, Belgium

- Development of audio-visual interactives
- Engineering & architecture of inhouse CMS platform to provide audio-visual interactives of content
- Development of custom CMS platforms as Lead Developer
- Development of custom software solutions

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER (INTERN)

February 2017 - June 2017 | University of the Western Cape

Cape Town, South Africa

- Internship at the Colab for Social Innovation and E-Inclusion
- Development of the University app to create micro-communities on campus
- Guiding starting Computer Science students on their path to become a software developer
- Briefing of stakeholders about upcoming features and releases
- Charity work by giving Java-classes to high-school students around Cape Town.